No, the uniform looks good on you.
いや、制服似合うね
amazing.
すごい
Do you usually wear a uniform?
普段は制服?
Yes, it's a similar uniform.
はい、なんか似たような感じの制服です
Ah, are they similar?
あ、似てる?
Is it like this?
こんな感じなの?
Laser?
レーザー?
yes.
はい
Just bring it sometime.
ちょっと今度持ってきて
Your hair is so smooth.
髪サラサラだよね
There's no need to touch it today.
今日触るの無しですよね
I just want to take pictures.
撮るだけなんで
Just take pictures?
撮るだけ?
yes.
はい
It's okay to take pictures.
撮ってはいいのね
It's really smooth.
ほんとすべすべだよね
Hey, just don't touch me.
ちょっと、ちょっと触らないで
No.
ダメです
picture?
え?
why?
なんで?
Today I'm just going to take pictures.
撮るだけなんで今日は
How far can I photograph?
どこまで撮っていいの?
It's okay to take pictures, but what about monkeys?
撮るのはいいんですけど、 さるの?
Don't let me in after all.
やっぱり入れないで
That's right.
そうなんですよ
Your hair is smooth.
髪サラサラだね
what?
何?
I heard you were just going to take some pictures today.
今日ちょっと、 撮るだけって聞いてたんで
No, no.
違う、違う
It's amazing because her hair is so silky.
髪がタラタラだから、 すごいな
What kind of shampoo do you use?
どんなシャンプー使ってるのかな?
What kind of shampoo?
どんなシャンプー?
Ordinary.
普通の
i don't know.
知らない
Shall we hold hands?
手繋ぐの?
That's good, right?
それいいでしょ
Your hands are big.
手、大きいね
It was tiny.
ちっちゃかった
That's deep.
深いよね
It's smooth.
すべすべだもんね
yeah?
ん?
what?
何?
Not really, yes.
あんまり、はい
Just a little bit is fine.
ちょっとだけいいじゃん
flash.
フラッシュ
yes.
はい
what?
何?
It's okay, it's okay.
いいじゃん、いいじゃん
Just for a little while.
ちょっとだけだから
Just use it a little.
ちょっとだけ使って
You're in trouble for money right now.
お金困ってるでしょ、今
I just want to help.
ちょっと、 助けたい
Just give me a massage.
マッサージだけさせて
You're tired, aren't you?
疲れてるでしょ
Where are you tired?
どこ疲れてる?
shoulder.
肩
I don't know.
分かんない
shoulder.
肩
The shoulders are still in their growth stage, so this is the area.
肩は結構、 成長期だから、 この辺のとこ
It's okay, it's okay.
いいです、いいです
it's okay.
大丈夫です
why?
なんで?
No?
ダメ?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
I'll just add a little bit here.
ちょっとプラスするから、ここだけ
Let me massage you.
マ ッサージさせて
It's elaborate, I guess.
凝ってるね、やっぱね
It's elaborate, it's elaborate.
凝ってる、凝ってる
I understand.
分かるんだよ
Aren't I tired too?
私も疲れてるんじゃない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's elaborate.
凝 えてる
No?
ダメ?
That's tough.
厳しいね
it hurts.
痛い
it hurts?
痛い?
yes.
そう
yes,
そう、
Really.
本当 に
That's fine.
いいじゃん
what?
何?
Swan is sweet.
スワンは甘いの
So beautiful.
こんなにきれいな
I'll touch it.
触っちゃう
You touched it, right?
触っとったでしょ
do not have?
ない?
Do you understand?
わかってる?
I see.
わかるね
difficult.
難しい
Can I take a look?
ちょっと見るでいい?
contents.
中身
Don't you want to see inside?
中、見たくない?
I'm sleeping.
寝てるよ
Don't sleep.
寝てんじゃん
I'm sleeping.
寝 てんじゃん
No.
ダメ
I'm sleeping.
寝 てんじゃん
strict.
厳しい
Are you not sleeping?
寝てない?
I'm not sleeping.
寝てない
why?
なんで?
strict.
厳しい
Is it strict?
厳しいの?
But that's it.
でも、そのちいじゃん
I haven't slept.
寝 てない
I'm not sleeping.
寝てない
I'll give you some money.
ちょっとお金あげるじゃん
Class again.
クラスまた
Really.
本当に
why?
なんで?
You know, always.
知ってるでしょ、いつもだって
No.
ダメ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Really.
本当に
No.
ダメ
Seriously?
マジダメ?
There's no end to it when I take a cock like this.
こんなチンチン取っちゃって終わんないよ
Put on the rubber.
ゴムつけて
Rubber?
ゴム?
yes.
はい
But it's rubber and doesn't feel comfortable.
でも、ゴムで気持ちよくないから
absolute.
絶対
That's absolutely true.
それは絶対
You should just put some rubber on it.
ゴムつければいいじゃん
You do it all the time.
いつもしてるじゃん
Haven't you?
してないの?
Have you ever done it live?
生でしたことない?
No.
ないです
Rubber is good.
ゴムがいいじゃん
Yeah.
うん
Put on your hands and feet.
手足つけて
it hurts.
痛い
it hurts?
痛い?
Put your feet up.
足立てて
Put on your hands and feet.
手足つけて
Turn to Nekuri.
ねっくり向けろ
ah.
ああ
Go
ゴ
Take it off.
ム 外して
I put it out.
出しちゃった
I was surprised.
びっくりした
I hated it raw.
生で嫌がった
Because it was cute.
可愛かったから